bvibe.com 2019-05-13

# Privacy Policy | b-Vibe

## What Is Your Privacy Policy?

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which bvibe.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from Users (each, a “User”) of the [bvibe.com](https://www.bvibe.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by bvibe.com.

**Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register to use our site, place an order on our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and any connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, their name, email address, phone number, financial, and credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-Personal Identification Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web Browser Cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How We Use Collected Information**

bbvibe.com may collect and use User personal information for the following purposes:

  * \- To improve customer service. Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and needs more efficiently.
  * \- To personalize user experience.  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * \- To improve our Site.  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * \- To run a promotion, contest, survey or to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * \- To send periodic emails.  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include instructions on how to unsubscribe at the bottom of each email.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Compliance With Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

bvibe.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and, where appropriate, notify users by email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your Acceptance Of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Severability**

If for any reason part of this policy is found void or unforeseeable, it will be deemed severed from the remainder of the policy, which will continue in full force and effect.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [customerservice@bvibe.com](mailto:customerservice@bvibe.com)
